payproglobal.com 2013-04-20

# Privacy policy 1. PayPro Privacy Statement Your privacy is important to us - we would like to insure that you have a positive buying experience in our store and hope to be able to welcome you back many times. We have created a set of privacy rules for us and our suppliers in order to guarantee you maximum privacy when shopping at PayPro

Privacy policy
1. PayPro Privacy Statement
Your privacy is important to us - we would like to insure that you have a positive buying experience in our store
and hope to be able to welcome you back many times. We have created a set of privacy rules for us and our
suppliers in order to guarantee you maximum privacy when shopping at PayPro’s Web site. Please note that
certain information is necessary in order to fulfill your order and authorize your payment - however we do not
collect any data without your consent. This statement is based on the OECD guidelines for user privacy which you
will find below.
2. About PayPro
Today's information and communication technologies are a central part of PayPro's business activities. Our
principal activity is Downloadable Product Distribution Services for companies and buyers alike. Protecting your
privacy and your personal data is an important aspect of the way we create, organize and implement our activities
on-line and off-line.
Our privacy policy covers PayPro Global Inc. and its Web site(s), PayPro U.S. Inc. and PayPro Europe Limited:
PAYPRO GLOBAL, INC.
225 The East Mall, Suite 1117
Toronto, ON, M9B 0A9
Canada
URL: www.payproglobal.com
PAYPRO U.S. INC.
3635 Johnson Ave, Suite 6M
Bronx, 10463
USA
PAYPRO EUROPE LIMITED
Berkley Square House
Berkley Square
London, W1J 6BD
United Kingdom
If you have any questions about our privacy policy, please contact:
Name: Tibor Madjar
Address: 225 The East Mall, Suite 1117, Toronto, ON, M9B 0A9, Canada
Phone: +1-646-873-6857 Ext:704
Fax: +1-416-981-7818 attn: Tibor Madjar
URL: www.payproglobal.com
3. Purpose Specification and Data Collection
You can access our Web site home page and browse our sites without disclosing personal data. We collect your
personal data only with your knowledge or your consent. Aside from your automatically logged information, we do
not collect any other data about you. We collect the personal data that you volunteer on registration, order,

survey, competition, other forms or by email.
4. Cookies
We use cookies only with your explicit consent in order to hold session information, improve security during a
visitor's session online or improve the usability of our Web site during a visit.
We do not associate the information stored in a visitor's cookie with any other personal data about that visitor
without the user's prior consent. Each of our employees who have access to your personal data and are associated
with the processing of that data are required to respect the confidentiality of your personal data.
5. Visitor Choice
You may choose to receive promotional or marketing information from our Web sites if you choose to do so.
6. Disclosure
We only disclose personal data about our Web site's visitors to our associated companies and their Web sites or -
in case of electronic delivery - to the companies, from which you purchase products, for their information. They
are allowed to use this information to provide you with technical support, inform you of product
updates/upgrades or new releases. They are also required to allow you the ability to unsubscribe from their
mailings. Your personal data will not be disclosed to any other third party, especially not for the purpose of
mailings or any other marketing activity. We ensure that your personal data will not be disclosed to state
institutions and authorities except if required by law or other regulations.
7. Privacy Policy
We have implemented technology and security policies, rules and measures to protect the personal data that we
have under our control from: unauthorized access, improper use, alteration, unlawful or accidental destruction,
accidental loss.
8. Privacy Compliance Details
The Privacy Principles of the OECD Guidelines
- Collection Limitation Principle
There should be limits to the collection of personal data and any such data should be obtained by lawful and fair
means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the user.
- Data Quality Principle
Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which they are to be used, and, to the extent necessary for
those purposes, should be accurate complete and kept up-to-date.
- Purpose Specification Principle
The purpose for which personal data is collected should be specified no later than at the time of collection and the
subsequent use limited to the fulfillment of those purposes or such others as are not incompatible with those
purposes and as are specified on each occasion of change of purpose.
- Use Limitation Principle
Personal data should not be disclosed, made available or otherwise used for purposes other than those specified in
accordance with Paragraph 9 [Purpose Specification Principle] of the OECD Privacy Guidelines except:

a) with the consent of the data subject; or
b) by the authority of law.
- Security Safeguards Principle
Personal data should be protected by reasonable security safeguards against such risks as loss, unauthorized
access, destruction, use, modification or disclosure of data.
- Openness Principle
There should be a general policy of openness about developments, practices and policies with respect to personal
data. Means should be readily available by establishing the existence and nature of personal data, and the main
purposes of their use, as well as the identity and use of the Data Controller.
- Individual Participation Principle
An individual should have the right:
a) to obtain from a data controller, or otherwise, confirmation of whether or not the data controller has data
relating to him;
b) to have communicated to him data relating to him within a reasonable time; at a charge, if any, that is not
excessive; in a reasonable manner; and in a form that is readily intelligible to him;
c) to be given reasons if a request made under subparagraphs (a) and (b) is denied, and to be able to challenge
such denial; and
d) to challenge data relating to him and, if the challenge is successful to have the data erased, rectified, completed
or amended.
- Accountability Principle
A Data Controller should be accountable for complying with measures which give effect to the principles stated
above.
